a4academics.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy & Terms Of Service

## Privacy Policy

To use our site, registration is not mandatory. But to get latest and interesting updates, we suggest users to subscribe to our weekly newsletter. We assure you that we will NOT trade, rent or share your emails with any other third parties. We had implemented enough security mechanisms to protect your personal information, transaction information and data stored on our Site. We will use your email, if we need to notify you about important policy updates or to get feedback on topics you wish to read. If you feel that our email services is not adding value to you, you can unsubscribe from our newsletter, provided at the bottom of each email. 

### Non-personal identification information

For enhancing our site performance we may collect non-personal identification information such as browser name, operating system (OS) and Internet service provider (ISP) to analyse visitor profile, geography and improve site speed. 

### Web browser cookies

For faster loading of website, we will use browser "cookies" to store our website's Images, Stylesheet and Javascript files. Cookies are stored in the hard drive for record keeping purposes and to track information about them. Users have the right to disable cookies in their browser, or to alert them, when cookies are being sent. If the cookies are disabled, some parts of the Site may not function as desired. 

### Google Adsense

We are using Google Adsense to serve ads. Google's use of the DART cookie, enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, physical address, email address etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [Disable DART cookie](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

### Disclosure Regarding Google Display Advertising

We implement Google Analytics features that use Display Advertising information for Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. 

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising, to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, by going to the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

We, along with third-party vendors (including Google), use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookies) to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our website. You can read more about the cookies used by Google Analytics advertising features, by going to the [Google Analytics Privacy Policy page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). 

A4academics.com holds the right to update the privacy policy at any time. Updates will be posted on this page, we request users to visit this page frequently to check for any changes to stay updated. 

## Terms Of Service

### Acceptance Of Terms

This page states the Terms and Conditions under which you (Visitor) may visit this Web site and use our offerings for good. Please read this page carefully. If the Terms and Conditions stated here are not acceptable for you, we would request you to leave this site. A4Academics.com reserve their respective rights to update these Terms and Conditions at any time, without notice of you. We request to visit this page periodically to re-appraise yourself of the updated terms and conditions. 

### Terms of Use

The services offered by A4academics.com is intended to provide students and working professionals, access to a huge collection of articles related to Engineering, Interview, Placement Preparation, Career Guidance and Soft Skills. We believe in information sharing and empower users for career success. Articles published in this website is collected from our well wishers around the world. Even though we review and compile the articles send to us by our users, a4academics.com can’t guarantee the correctness of the information provided in those article and won’t be liable/responsible for any misappropriate content, suggestions, questions and answers or any other forms of errors. 

A4academics.com will not be liable for the consequences that might arise due to some misappropriate content or info in this site. Users submitting article to this site, declare that he/she have complete ownership of the data or has the right to redistribute it. A4academics.com won't assume liability for disputes arising due to copyright, trademarks or ownership of the data submitted. A4academics.com own the complete rights to edit, remove or refuse a submission made to the site, without any prior notice to the person submitting the article. Contents of this website is for private, non-profit use by you. 

### Anti-Spam Policy

A4academics.com is against sending spam or unsolicited emails. Don't use our newsletter or email services, for your personal or commercial purposes. If anyone finds violating our anti spam policies, necessary action will be initiated against the spammers. 

### Copyright Infringement Policy

All articles and data presented on this website are the property of A4academics.com. You are not entitled to reproduce or redistribute in any way, shape or form without the written permission of A4academics.com. A4academics.com respects the intellectual property and copyrights of others and we expect the same in return. If you found that that any of our articles is owned by you and it violates your intellectual property rights, please let us know about the same, along the substantial documents that proves your ownership. We will remove those articles from our site ASAP. Also if you find any of our content as objectionable, harmful, threatening, abusive, defamatory, vulgar or invasive of another person’s privacy, mail us. We will take necessary action. 

If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Phone - **+91-9480369000**

Email - **info@a4academics.com**
